<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Ryan Menezes</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Ryan Menezes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Ryan Menezes. Here are some things you ought to know about me:
From 2013 to 2021 I was a journalist at the Los Angeles Times, where I analyzed data for stories across different subjects. As a member of the Data and Graphics team, I also wrote stories, crafted visualizations and tackled random journalistic problems with the help of code.
My job at The Times combined two of my passions: storytelling and data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>L.A. Times portfolio</title>
      <link>/portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/</guid>
      <description>I joined the L.A. Times in 2013 as a fellow in the Metpro training program. Across nearly eight years as a journalist there, I covered a variety of topics, always with an eye towards telling compelling stories after thorough data analysis. I utilized a variety of technical tools to accomplish this: R or python as an everyday starting point with data, QGIS for geospatial analysis, PostgreSQL databases for especially large queries and the front-end development stack of HTML, CSS and JavaScript to publish my work for a digital audience, with the help of the d3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon: Personal projects</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
